<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.5.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://d2m.tech/webpacked-jekyll-assets-minima/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://d2m.tech/webpacked-jekyll-assets-minima/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2017-08-04T17:36:56+02:00</updated><id>https://d2m.tech/webpacked-jekyll-assets-minima/</id><title type="html">Your awesome title</title><subtitle>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Welcome to Jekyll!</title><link href="https://d2m.tech/webpacked-jekyll-assets-minima/jekyll/update/2017/07/12/welcome-to-jekyll.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Welcome to Jekyll!" /><published>2017-07-12T00:15:51+02:00</published><updated>2017-07-12T00:15:51+02:00</updated><id>https://d2m.tech/webpacked-jekyll-assets-minima/jekyll/update/2017/07/12/welcome-to-jekyll</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://d2m.tech/webpacked-jekyll-assets-minima/jekyll/update/2017/07/12/welcome-to-jekyll.html">&lt;p&gt;You’ll find this post in your &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_posts&lt;/code&gt; directory. Go ahead and edit it and re-build the site to see your changes. You can rebuild the site in many different ways, but the most common way is to run &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;jekyll serve&lt;/code&gt;, which launches a web server and auto-regenerates your site when a file is updated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To add new posts, simply add a file in the &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_posts&lt;/code&gt; directory that follows the convention &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;YYYY-MM-DD-name-of-post.ext&lt;/code&gt; and includes the necessary front matter. Take a look at the source for this post to get an idea about how it works.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jekyll also offers powerful support for code snippets:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-ruby&quot; data-lang=&quot;ruby&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;def&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;puts&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;Hi, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;#{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;end&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;'Tom'&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;c1&quot;&gt;#=&amp;gt; prints 'Hi, Tom' to STDOUT.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check out the &lt;a href=&quot;https://jekyllrb.com/docs/home&quot;&gt;Jekyll docs&lt;/a&gt; for more info on how to get the most out of Jekyll. File all bugs/feature requests at &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/jekyll/jekyll&quot;&gt;Jekyll’s GitHub repo&lt;/a&gt;. If you have questions, you can ask them on &lt;a href=&quot;https://talk.jekyllrb.com/&quot;&gt;Jekyll Talk&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">You’ll find this post in your _posts directory. Go ahead and edit it and re-build the site to see your changes. You can rebuild the site in many different ways, but the most common way is to run jekyll serve, which launches a web server and auto-regenerates your site when a file is updated.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">She tried pesto for the first time Imagine.</title><link href="https://d2m.tech/webpacked-jekyll-assets-minima/jekyll/update/2016/12/03/she-tried-pesto-for-the-first-time-imagine.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="She tried pesto for the first time Imagine." /><published>2016-12-03T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2016-12-03T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>https://d2m.tech/webpacked-jekyll-assets-minima/jekyll/update/2016/12/03/she-tried-pesto-for-the-first-time-imagine</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://d2m.tech/webpacked-jekyll-assets-minima/jekyll/update/2016/12/03/she-tried-pesto-for-the-first-time-imagine.html">&lt;p&gt;She tried pesto for the first time. Imagine that, 92 years old and she never tried pesto. What’s gotten into you? Have you been eating cheese? If I look like a man who made love to his wife last night – it’s because I almost did. And I wouldn’t just lie there, if that’s what you’re thinking.  That’s not what I WAS thinking. I hear the jury’s still out on science. It’s a wonderful restaurant! I prematurely shot my wad on what was supposed to be a dry run..so now I’m afraid I have something of a mess on my hands.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Operation Hot Mother. So did you see the new Poof? His name’s Gary, and we don’t need anymore lawsuits. I’m going to buy you the single healthiest call girl this town has ever seen. Even though so many people in this office are begging for it. Well, yeah you’ve gotta lock that down. Of course. The “Bob Loblaw Law Blog.” Wow. You, sir, are a mouthful! Dad asked me to do this on the day he pleads not guilty, as a spectacular protest. A…. ? If you’re suggesting I play favorites, you’re wrong. I love all of my children equally. I don’t care for Gob.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I run a pretty tight ship around here. With a pool table. Coo coo ca chaw. Coo coo ca chaw. I could use a leather jacket for when I’m on my hog and have to go into a controlled slide. Happy. Do the right thing here. String this blind girl along so that dad doesn’t have to pay his debt to society. I’d rather be dead in California than alive in Arizona. I’ve made a huge tiny mistake. But I did finally get into Dad’s pants. Although I had to have the crotch taken in a little bit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Heyyyy Uncle Father Oscar. A sea of waiters and no one will take a drink order. Yeah, like anyone would want to R her. It was for me. I was going to smoke the marijuana like a cigarette. Gosh Mom… after all these years, God’s not going to take a call from you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Actually, that was a box of Oscar’s legally obtained medical marijuana. Primo bud. Real sticky weed. Her lawyers are claiming the seal is worth $250,000. And that’s not even including Buster’s Swatch. I should be in this Poof. It’s a jetpack, Michael. What could go wrong? How about a turtle? I’ve always loved those leathery little snappy faces.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If this were a Lifetime Moment of Truth movie, this would be our act break.  But it wasn’t. Oh by the way, Doctor said no kissing her on the face for one week. I was like make it two weeks, see if I care! Are you sure this isn’t her sister? Mrs Veal: What a lovely thing to say. Michael: That’s an awful thing to say. Ah, it is a rock, though. Should beat everything. Gob: There’s not a lot of logic to it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes, he’s like the steel man from The Wizard From Oz. Perhaps an attic shall I seek. This is the best free scrapbooking class I’ve ever taken! And don’t make the water too hot. The scabs come right off. ♪♪ It ain’t easy being white. It ain’t easy being brown. ♪♪ Happy Franklin Friday. I guess you can say I’m buy-curious. Bob Loblaw Law Blog.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gosh Mom… after all these years, God’s not going to take a call from you. Hey, it was one night of wild passion! And yet you didn’t notice her body? I like to look in the mirror. So you take your mom to work every day? Bummer. Moms are such a pain in the ass, huh? It’s, like, die already!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It just seems like there’s still light coming in from under the door. We have unlimited juice? This party is going to be off the hook. I’m going to buy you the single healthiest call girl this town has ever seen. It’s sort of like going from prime rib to… I don’t know… weird brother of prime rib.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh, COME ON! Buster, you remember when we were kissing last night? Buster: It was a wild, wild ride. Ann certainly has a great deal of Mass. I just don’t want him to point out my cracker ass in front of Ann. You must teach me the ways of the secular flesh.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">She tried pesto for the first time. Imagine that, 92 years old and she never tried pesto. What’s gotten into you? Have you been eating cheese? If I look like a man who made love to his wife last night – it’s because I almost did. And I wouldn’t just lie there, if that’s what you’re thinking. That’s not what I WAS thinking. I hear the jury’s still out on science. It’s a wonderful restaurant! I prematurely shot my wad on what was supposed to be a dry run..so now I’m afraid I have something of a mess on my hands.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Talk you off what Pop Pop Well yeah.</title><link href="https://d2m.tech/webpacked-jekyll-assets-minima/jekyll/update/2016/12/01/talk-you-off-what-pop-pop-well-yeah.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Talk you off what Pop Pop Well yeah." /><published>2016-12-01T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2016-12-01T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>https://d2m.tech/webpacked-jekyll-assets-minima/jekyll/update/2016/12/01/talk-you-off-what-pop-pop-well-yeah</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://d2m.tech/webpacked-jekyll-assets-minima/jekyll/update/2016/12/01/talk-you-off-what-pop-pop-well-yeah.html">&lt;p&gt;Talk you off what, Pop Pop? Well, yeah you’ve gotta lock that down.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am going to my spin class. I thought you had vertigo. You just made a fool out of yourself in front of T-Bone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’ll have to find something to do so that people can look at you without wanting to kill themselves. And with deep, deep concentration and, and great focus, he’s often able to achieve an erect– I made a huge tiny mistake. Oh, I don’t have any drugs for sale, unless… did you want me to follow you to your car? She’s a contestant. It’s sorta like an inner beauty pageant. Ah, there it is. These are my awards, Mother. From Army. The seal is for marksmanship, and the gorilla is for sand racing. For the same reason you should believe a hundred dollar bill is no more than a hundred pennies!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Operation Hot Mother. Her lawyers are claiming the seal is worth $250,000. And that’s not even including Buster’s Swatch. What do you think about Sudden Valley? It sounds like a salad dressing, but for some reason I don’t want to eat it. Oh, COME ON! You boys know how to shovel coal? A trick is something a whore does for money…or candy.  … or cocaine. ♪♪ It ain’t easy being white. It ain’t easy being brown. ♪♪ Oh, yes, there absolutely will be a margarita made in my mouth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;♪♪ Somewhere… over the rainbow… there’s another rainbow… ♪♪ Did you know that more frozen bananas are sold right here on this boardwalk than anywhere in the OC? I want to cry so bad, but I don’t think I can spare the moisture. Yes, Annyong. Your name is Annyong! We all know you’re Annyong! I’m not a prostitute. Michael: Then I shall let you live! Well, OK, have sex with this girl. Right now. Get in there, have some sex with her. Oh, hi, Mom. I have the afternoon free. Really? Did “nothing” cancel?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even though sooooo many people in this office are begging for it. Yes. Lindsay and I are planning a night of heterosexual intercourse. So, what do you say? We got a basket full of father-son fun here. What’s Kama Sutra oil? Maybe it’s not for us. Wow. We’re just blowing through nap time, aren’t we? Do you have any idea how often you say the word “afraid”? Well, I know I used it in the Jacuzzi. Let me out that Queen. Look at us, crying like a couple of girls on the last day of camp. No, it’s the opposite. It’s like my heart is getting hard.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A million [bleep]ing diamonds! Mister gay is bleeding! Mister gay! The only thing more terrifying than the escaped lunatic’s hook was his twisted call… Hey campers! Heyyyyyy Uncle Father Oscar. It’s a wonderful restaurant! Daddy horny, Michael. Wine only turns to alcohol if you let it sit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hola, is Rosa still alive? No? Well this is not my day. I just dont want him to point out my cracker ass in front of Ann. Are you at all concerned about an uprising?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the guys told me to take my head out of my BOTTOM and get back to work…my BOTTOM! I could use a leather jacket for when I’m on my hog and have to go into a controlled slide. Happy. Yeah, well, have you seen the new Mustang? You could hump that hood. Tobias is Queen Mary. Look at us, crying like a bunch of girls on the last day of camp. Whoa whoa whoa whoa. Wait. Are you telling me you have a multi-stage trick with hidden identities?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Teamocil. What do you think about Sudden Valley? It sounds like a salad dressing, but for some reason I don’t want to eat it. Pound is tic-tac-toe right? I figured out a way to make money while I’m working!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Talk you off what, Pop Pop? Well, yeah you’ve gotta lock that down.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">I m a complete failure I can t.</title><link href="https://d2m.tech/webpacked-jekyll-assets-minima/jekyll/update/2016/11/17/i-m-a-complete-failure-i-can-t.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="I m a complete failure I can t." /><published>2016-11-17T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2016-11-17T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>https://d2m.tech/webpacked-jekyll-assets-minima/jekyll/update/2016/11/17/i-m-a-complete-failure-i-can-t</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://d2m.tech/webpacked-jekyll-assets-minima/jekyll/update/2016/11/17/i-m-a-complete-failure-i-can-t.html">&lt;p&gt;I’m a complete failure. I can’t even fake the death of a stripper. With spicy club sauce.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If this were a Lifetime Moment of Truth movie, this would be our act break.  But it wasn’t. Okay, Lindsay, are you forgetting that I was a professional twice over - an analyst and a therapist. The world’s first analrapist. Chickens don’t clap! It’s, like, Hey, you want to go down to the whirlpool? Yeah, I don’t have a husband. I call it Swing City. Oh, COME ON!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hate the Wetlands. They’re stupid and wet, and there are bugs everywhere, and I think I maced a crane. Hey, it was one night of wild passion! And yet you didn’t notice her body? I like to look in the mirror. But anyhoo, can you believe that the only reason the club is going under is because it’s in a terrifying neighborhood? It’s as Ann as the nose on plain’s face.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No, Pop-pop does not get a treat. I just bought you a f**king pizza. How do you know Steve Holt? Are you in AA? I spent so much time making sweet love on my wife that it’s hard to hear anything over the clatter of her breasts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please refrain from Mayoneggs during this salmonella scare. I need a fake passport, preferably to France… I like the way they think. George Michael, you want to put your head down there by his drainage shunt? Okay, Lindsay, are you forgetting that I was a professional twice over - an analyst and a therapist. The world’s first analrapist. I’m sure Egg is a great person. Wow. We’re just blowing through nap time, aren’t we.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Make love in your &lt;em&gt;own&lt;/em&gt; hand, Mother! I cheated and I lied and I whored around. So did you see the new Poof? His name’s Gary and we don’t need anymore lawsuits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh, I don’t have any drugs for sale, unless… did you want me to follow you to your car? Can’t a guy call his mother pretty without it seeming strange? Amen. And how about that little piece of tail on her? Cute! I may have committed some light treason. Mom… after all these years, God’s not going to take a call from you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am going to my spin class. I thought you had vertigo. It seems like only yesterday you were bursting forth from your mother’s fertile womb.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I prematurely shot my wad on what was supposed to be a dry run..so now I’m afraid I have something of a mess on my hands. Shémale. I’m not a prostitute. Michael: Then I shall let you live! It’s ok. You be with Yam. Oh, yes, there absolutely will be a margarita made in my mouth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ll be in the hospital bar. You know there isn’t a hospital bar, Mother. Well, this is why people hate hospitals. I’ve made a huge tiny mistake. I believe you will find the dessert to be both engrossing and high-grossing!  So we don’t get dessert? You might enjoy this.  Oh. Em. Gee. That’s amazing. Heart attack never stopped old big bear! I’ve made a huge tiny mistake. Absolutely. And we’re going to be here every day. I don’t care if it takes from now till the end of Shrimpfest.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I’m a complete failure. I can’t even fake the death of a stripper. With spicy club sauce.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Are you sure this isn t her sister.</title><link href="https://d2m.tech/webpacked-jekyll-assets-minima/jekyll/update/2016/11/16/are-you-sure-this-isn-t-her-sister.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Are you sure this isn t her sister." /><published>2016-11-16T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2016-11-16T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>https://d2m.tech/webpacked-jekyll-assets-minima/jekyll/update/2016/11/16/are-you-sure-this-isn-t-her-sister</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://d2m.tech/webpacked-jekyll-assets-minima/jekyll/update/2016/11/16/are-you-sure-this-isn-t-her-sister.html">&lt;p&gt;Are you sure this isn’t her sister? Mrs Veal: What a lovely thing to say. Michael: That’s an awful thing to say. I will pack your sweet pink mouth with so much ice cream you’ll be the envy of every Jerry and Jane on the block!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This objectification of women has to stop. It’s just Mom and whores. Operation Hot Mother. It looks like you’ve been looking for dragons… in the future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Friday night. Do the right thing here. String this blind girl along so that dad doesn’t have to pay his debt to society. Whoa whoa whoa whoa. Wait. Are you telling me you have a multi-stage trick with hidden identities? George Bush doesn’t care about black puppets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;♪♪ It’s The Final Countdown ♪♪ There’s unlimited juice? This party is gonna be off the hook. Let me take off my assistant’s skirt and put on my Barbra-Streisand-in-The-Prince-of-Tides ass-masking therapist pantsuit. Got a big ass room at the travelodge.  What a fun, sexy time for you. Smack of ham. What is she doing at a beauty pageant? Is she running the lights or something? She calls it a mayonegg.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Talk you off what, Pop Pop? Quicken! Premiere! Dad would stage elaborate situations using a one-armed man to teach us lessons. And that is why Jesus was often referred to as the King of Kings. Queens. The King of Queens. No, no, it’s pronounced a-nal-ra-pist.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Someone order 140 pounds of upper body strength? A trick is something a whore does for money…or candy.  … or cocaine. Probably out there without a flipper, swimming around in a circle, freaking out his whole family. If I make this comeback, I’ll buy you a hundred George Michaels that you can teach to drive!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’re blowing my mind, Frank. Ah, it is a rock, though. Should beat everything. Gob: There’s not a lot of logic to it. She keeps saying that God is going to show me a sign. The… something of my ways. Wisdom? Hair up, glasses off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh by the way, Doctor said no kissing her on the face for one week. I was like make it two weeks, see if I care! WHY was this show cancelled? I mean, COME ON. Even it means me taking a chubby… I will suck it up. I just haven’t had sex in a month. You know, you’ve been here two months. It’s hard to gauge time. Get rid of the Seaward. Lucille: I’ll leave when I’m good and ready. Dead Dove DO NOT EAT. You might enjoy this.  Oh. Em. Gee. That’s amazing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s one banana Michael, what could it cost, ten dollars? A Colombian cartel that WON’T kidnap and kill you. [climbing under trampoline] This shall keep me safe from the hot Mexican sun. I’m not a prostitute. Then I shall let you live! I don’t want no part of yo tight-ass country-club, ya freak bitch! Do the right thing here. String this blind girl along so that dad doesn’t have to pay his debt to society.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s, like, Hey, you want to go down to the whirlpool? Yeah, I don’t have a husband. I call it Swing City. Michael was concerned that he was caught in a lie about his family. The family was concerned that they were being confronted by a woman they had clubbed, drugged, and left on a bench. I call it Tricks –- wait for it – Around The Office. I think the only time you cooked for us was the morning Rosa’s mom died. You gave us cereal in an ashtray.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Are you sure this isn’t her sister? Mrs Veal: What a lovely thing to say. Michael: That’s an awful thing to say. I will pack your sweet pink mouth with so much ice cream you’ll be the envy of every Jerry and Jane on the block!</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Annyong I will pack your sweet pink mouth.</title><link href="https://d2m.tech/webpacked-jekyll-assets-minima/jekyll/update/2016/11/08/annyong-i-will-pack-your-sweet-pink-mouth.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Annyong I will pack your sweet pink mouth." /><published>2016-11-08T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2016-11-08T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>https://d2m.tech/webpacked-jekyll-assets-minima/jekyll/update/2016/11/08/annyong-i-will-pack-your-sweet-pink-mouth</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://d2m.tech/webpacked-jekyll-assets-minima/jekyll/update/2016/11/08/annyong-i-will-pack-your-sweet-pink-mouth.html">&lt;p&gt;Annyong. I will pack your sweet pink mouth with so much ice cream you’ll be the envy of every Jerry and Jane on the block! The only thing I found in the fridge was a dead dove in a bag. Gob: You didn’t eat that, did you? What’s next, Michael? Are you going to make dancing illegal? Is this the tiny town from Footloose? If this were a Lifetime Moment of Truth movie, this would be our act break.  But it wasn’t. She’s not ‘that Mexican’, Mom. She’s my Mexican. And she’s Colombian or something.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stop it, stop it. This objectification of women has to stop. It’s just Mom and whores. Boy, I sure feel like a Mary without a Peter and a Paul. Oh, I don’t have any drugs for sale, unless… did you want me to follow you to your car?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Turn this skiff around! Or it could be your colon. I’d want to get in there and find some answers. I know she’s a brownish area! With points! And I love her! She’s always got to wedge herself in the middle of us so that she can control everything. Yeah. Mom’s awesome. You burn down the storage unit? Oh, most definitely. Hey, Dad. Look at you. You’re a year older…and a year closer to death. Buster: Oh yeah, I guess that’s kind of funny. No. I was ashamed to be &lt;em&gt;seen&lt;/em&gt; with you. I like being with you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, I spent so much time making sweet love on my wife that it’s hard to hear anything over the clatter of her breasts. I deceived you, mom. Tricked makes it sound like we have a playful relationship. I’ve been in the film business for a while but I just can’t seem to get one in the can. Well, OK, have sex with this girl. Right now. Get in there, have some sex with her. I think the only time you cooked for us was the morning Rosa’s mom died. You gave us cereal in an ashtray. Even though so many people in this office are begging for it. When a.. man.. needs to prove to a woman that he’s actually.. [pause].. When a man loves a woman.. I’m not a prostitute. Then I shall let you live!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nellie is blowing them all AWAY. Am I in two thirds of a hospital room? Turn this skiff around! ♪♪ It ain’t easy being white… ♪♪ Dead Dove DO NOT EAT. I know what an erection feels like, Michael. No, it’s the opposite. It’s like my heart is getting hard. Stop it, stop it. This objectification of women has to stop. It’s just Mom and whores.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re suggesting I play favorites, you’re wrong. I love all of my children equally. I don’t care for Gob. I know what an erection feels like, Michael.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Or it could be your colon. I’d want to get in there and find some answers. Touché, Pandora. Buster’s in what we like to call a light to no coma. In laymans terms, it might be considered a very heavy nap. I made a huge tiny mistake. I’m not a prostitute. Michael: Then I shall let you live! Could it be love? I know what an erection feels like, Michael. No, it’s the opposite… like my heart is getting hard.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He also said some things African American-y wasn’t ready to hear. Probably out there without a flipper, swimming around in a circle, freaking out his whole family.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s make Ann the backup, okay? Very good way to think about her, as a backup. I need a fake passport, preferably to France…I like the way they think. If I look like a man who made love to his wife last night – it’s because I almost did. I’ve always been deeply passionate about nature. Perhaps you remember Neuterfest? M: I’ll never forget your wedding. I know what an erection feels like, Michael. No, it’s the opposite. It’s like my heart is getting hard. I am going to my spin class. I thought you had vertigo. That was Tom Cruise, the actor. They said he was some kind of scientist.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m sure, wherever your father is, she loves you very much. And I wouldn’t just lie there, if that’s what you’re thinking.  That’s not what I WAS thinking. I’ve been in the film business for a while but I just can’t seem to get one in the can. Say something that will terrify me. Lindsay: F*** me. Tobias: No, that didn’t do it.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Annyong. I will pack your sweet pink mouth with so much ice cream you’ll be the envy of every Jerry and Jane on the block! The only thing I found in the fridge was a dead dove in a bag. Gob: You didn’t eat that, did you? What’s next, Michael? Are you going to make dancing illegal? Is this the tiny town from Footloose? If this were a Lifetime Moment of Truth movie, this would be our act break. But it wasn’t. She’s not ‘that Mexican’, Mom. She’s my Mexican. And she’s Colombian or something.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">You re losing blood aren t you Probably.</title><link href="https://d2m.tech/webpacked-jekyll-assets-minima/jekyll/update/2016/11/06/you-re-losing-blood-aren-t-you-probably.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="You re losing blood aren t you Probably." /><published>2016-11-06T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2016-11-06T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>https://d2m.tech/webpacked-jekyll-assets-minima/jekyll/update/2016/11/06/you-re-losing-blood-aren-t-you-probably</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://d2m.tech/webpacked-jekyll-assets-minima/jekyll/update/2016/11/06/you-re-losing-blood-aren-t-you-probably.html">&lt;p&gt;You’re losing blood, aren’t you? Probably, my socks are wet. You want to have some guy reach around you in the middle of the night, start messing with your junk? A lady of the evening. Working girl. She turns illusions for money. Talk you off what, Pop Pop? Fun and failure both start out the same way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well excuse me, Judge Reinhold! And although the intervention didn’t work, it turned into one of the Bluth family’s better parties. And don’t make the water too hot. The scabs come right off. One of the guys told me to take my head out of my BOTTOM and get back to work…my BOTTOM! I’m an ideas man, Michael. I think I proved that with “Fuck Mountain.” Well, Michael, I did not find their buffoonery amusing. Well excuse me for liking the way they frame my junk! Oh, hi, Mom. I have the afternoon free. Really? Did “nothing” cancel?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When a man needs to prove to a woman that he’s actually… When a man loves a woman… Ah, it is a rock, though. Should beat everything. Gob: There’s not a lot of logic to it. It’s so watery. And yet there’s a smack of ham to it. I’ve been in the film business for a while but I just can’t seem to get one in the can. Hey, it was one night of wild passion! Michael: And yet you didn’t notice her body? Gob: I like to look in the mirror. I don’t care if it takes from now till the end of Shrimpfest. If I wanted something your thumb touched, I’d eat the inside of your ear.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can control your bladder when you’re dead! It walked on my pillow! You’re Killing Me, Buster. The only thing more terrifying than the escaped lunatic’s hook was his twisted call… Heyyyyy campers!  You’re Killing Me, Buster. It’s sort of like going from prime rib to… I don’t know… weird brother of prime rib.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Probably out there without a flipper, swimming around in a circle, freaking out his whole family. Operation Hot Mother. Chicken fingers… with spicy club sauce. What a fun, sexy time for you. Heyyyyy, hermano.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, I hope you also carry a spare bowl of candy beans. You boys know how to shovel coal? You’re a good guy, mon frere. That means brother in French. I don’t know how I know that. I took four years of Spanish.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;GENE!! [screams] Dad asked me to do this on the day he pleads not guilty, as a spectacular protest. A…. ? I need a tea to give my dingle less tingle. Butterscotch! Want a lick? In prison, you just have to close your eyes and take it, but here you have to close your eyes and give it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you don’t start pulling your weight around here its going to be shape up, or…ship up. Ann, you need to decide whether you want a man or a boy. I know how I’d answer. She calls it a mayonegg.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I never thought I’d miss a hand so much! We have unlimited juice? This party is going to be off the hook. Michael, you are not quite the ladies man I had pictured. Hopefully, we will remedy that when we are in the spa spreading body chocolate on each other.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Heart attack never stopped old big bear. Yeah, I invited her. You said you wanted to spend time some with her. You said I was being an Ann hog. Hey, it was one night of wild passion! And yet you didn’t notice her body? I like to look in the mirror. Heart attack never stopped old big bear. And I wouldn’t just lie there, if that’s what you’re thinking.  That’s not what I WAS thinking.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">You’re losing blood, aren’t you? Probably, my socks are wet. You want to have some guy reach around you in the middle of the night, start messing with your junk? A lady of the evening. Working girl. She turns illusions for money. Talk you off what, Pop Pop? Fun and failure both start out the same way.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">It ain t easy being white Did.</title><link href="https://d2m.tech/webpacked-jekyll-assets-minima/jekyll/update/2016/11/04/it-ain-t-easy-being-white-did.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title=" It ain t easy being white Did." /><published>2016-11-04T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2016-11-04T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>https://d2m.tech/webpacked-jekyll-assets-minima/jekyll/update/2016/11/04/it-ain-t-easy-being-white-did</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://d2m.tech/webpacked-jekyll-assets-minima/jekyll/update/2016/11/04/it-ain-t-easy-being-white-did.html">&lt;p&gt;♪♪ It ain’t easy being white… ♪♪ Did you know that more frozen bananas are sold right here on this boardwalk than anywhere on the OC? The only person that gets Lucille this excited is Gene.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chickens don’t clap! Chaw-chee, chaw-chee chaw-chee! Coo coo ca cha! Ah coodle doodle do Caw ca caw, caw ca caw. And I am rock steady. No more dizzies. You just made a fool out of yourself in front of T-Bone. YOU’RE the Chiclet! Not me. Caw ca caw, caw ca caw, caw ca caw! Oh, hi, Mom. I have the afternoon free. Really? Did “nothing” cancel? You boys know how to shovel coal? Never once touched my per diem. I’d go to Craft Service, get some raw veggies, bacon, Cup-A-Soup…baby, I got a stew goin’.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fried cheese… with club sauce. Fried cheese… with club sauce.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve always been deeply passionate about nature. Perhaps you remember Neuterfest? M: I’ll never forget your wedding. She calls it a mayonegg. I know, I just call her Annabelle cause she’s shaped like a… she’s the belle of the ball! The Army had half a day. What do you expect, Mother? I’m half machine! I’m a monster!! Touché, Pandora. Ann, you need to decide whether you want a man or a boy. I know how I’d answer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sweet old thing. Only two of those words describe Mom, so I know you’re lying to me. Get rid of the Seaward. Lucille: I’ll leave when I’m good and ready. How about a turtle? I’ve always loved those leathery little snappy faces. Saw this on the highway and almost blue myself.  Hop on? In the mid ’90s, Tobias formed a folk music band with Lindsay and Maebe which he called Dr. Funke’s 100 Percent Natural Good Time Family Band Solution. The group was underwritten by the Natural Food Life Company, a division of Chem-Grow, an Allen Crayne acqusition, which was part of the Squimm Group. Their motto was simple: We keep you alive. I’m an ideas man, Michael. I think I proved that with “Fuck Mountain.” Go ahead, touch the cornballer. Buster’s in what we like to call a light to no coma. In laymans terms, it might be considered a very heavy nap.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;♪♪ Big yellow joint, big yellow joint, I’ll meet you down at the big yellow joint. ♪♪ Bob Loblaw Law Blog. I’d rather be dead in California than alive in Arizona. I think that’s one of Mom’s little fibs, you know, like I’ll sacrifice anything for my children. Ann, you need to decide whether you want a man or a boy. I know how I’d answer. I was hoping he would be gifted sexually.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t call my escorts whores. Oh by the way, Doctor said no kissing her on the face for one week. I was like make it two weeks, see if I care! Yeah, well, have you seen the new Mustang? You could hump that hood. Although George Michael had only got to second base, he’d gone in head first, like Pete Rose. I’m in Vegas this week and would like to point out the Blue Man Group is &lt;em&gt;actually&lt;/em&gt; hiring. The support group? I’m not a prostitute. Michael: Then I shall let you live!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is not what it looks like. It looks like you’re tweaking her nipples through a chain-link fence. Look at us, crying like a couple of girls on the last day of camp. Although George Michael had only got to second base, he’d gone in head first, like Pete Rose.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She keeps saying that God is going to show me a sign. The… something of my ways. Wisdom? It’s probably wisdom. I spent so much time making sweet love on my wife that it’s hard to hear anything over the clatter of her breasts. I’ll have a vodka rocks. (Mom, it’s breakfast time.) And a piece of toast. Oh, yeah, the $4,000 suit is holding the elevator for a guy who doesn’t make that in 3 months. Come on! Everyone’s laughing, and riding, and cornholing except Buster.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Man Inside Me seems well reviewed. I need a tea to give my dingle less tingle. For the same reason you should believe a hundred dollar bill is no more than a hundred pennies!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">♪♪ It ain’t easy being white… ♪♪ Did you know that more frozen bananas are sold right here on this boardwalk than anywhere on the OC? The only person that gets Lucille this excited is Gene.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">You burn down the storage unit Oh most.</title><link href="https://d2m.tech/webpacked-jekyll-assets-minima/jekyll/update/2016/11/01/you-burn-down-the-storage-unit-oh-most.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="You burn down the storage unit Oh most." /><published>2016-11-01T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2016-11-01T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>https://d2m.tech/webpacked-jekyll-assets-minima/jekyll/update/2016/11/01/you-burn-down-the-storage-unit-oh-most</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://d2m.tech/webpacked-jekyll-assets-minima/jekyll/update/2016/11/01/you-burn-down-the-storage-unit-oh-most.html">&lt;p&gt;You burn down the storage unit? Oh, most definitely. After all, why should you go to jail for a crime somebody else noticed? And don’t make the water too hot. The scabs come right off. And guess what else is back. [slow wink] My breakfast? My friskiness. Mama horny Michael. Monday morning. COME ON! Teamocil. Or it could be your colon. I’d want to get in there and find some answers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, obviously, I’m not a big guy. I’m not a Carl Weathers, par example. I’ll be in the hospital bar. You know there isn’t a hospital bar, Mother. Well, this is why people hate hospitals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am having a love affair with this ice cream sandwich. I didn’t mean who… I meant… her? Oh, I don’t have any drugs for sale, unless… did you want me to follow you to your car? I cheated and I lied and I whored around. But where did the lighter fluid come from? Yeah, like I’m going to spill coffee all over this $3,000 suit? Come on! If I make this comeback, I’ll buy you a hundred George Michaels that you can teach to drive!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I made a huge tiny mistake. Why are you squeezing me with your body? Well, I hope you also carry a spare bowl of candy beans. Shémale. Here he comes. Here comes John Wayne.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They’re not gonna strip, right? I told them not to, but I can’t guarantee their instincts won’t kick in. O-kay, who’d like a banger in the mouth? Hey, Dad. Look at you. You’re a year older…and a year closer to death. Buster: Oh yeah, I guess that’s kind of funny. What’s gotten into you? Have you been eating cheese?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whenever she’d change clothes, she’d make me wait on the balcony until zip-up, and yet anything goes at bath time. Coo coo ca chaw. Coo coo ca chaw. Coo coo ca chaw. Stop it, stop it. This objectification of women has to stop. Michael: It’s just Mom and whores.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maybe it was the eleven months he spent in the womb. The doctor said there were claw marks on the walls of her uterus. It’s a jetpack, Michael. What could go wrong? Michael, look, this has got to stop. I mean, flattered? Yes. Interested? Not tonight. You need to do more with Rita. Believe me, I’d like to. Caw ca caw, caw ca caw, caw ca caw, caw ca caw. What’s up, fizz-ellas. Everybody dance NOW.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Coo coo ca chaw. Coo coo ca chaw. It’s a jetpack, Michael. What could go wrong? Heart attack never stopped old big bear. You’re losing blood, aren’t you? Gob: Probably, my socks are wet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interfere? I ought to pull down your pants and spank your ass raw. Michael: I’m sorry, have we met? Ann certainly has a great deal of Mass. You’re losing blood, aren’t you? Probably, my socks are wet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m gonna build me an airport, put my name on it. Why, Michael? So you can fly away from your feelings? Sweet old thing. Only two of those words describe Mom, so I know you’re lying to me. I will pack your sweet pink mouth with so much ice cream you’ll be the envy of every Jerry and Jane on the block! Stop licking my hand, you horse’s ass!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">You burn down the storage unit? Oh, most definitely. After all, why should you go to jail for a crime somebody else noticed? And don’t make the water too hot. The scabs come right off. And guess what else is back. [slow wink] My breakfast? My friskiness. Mama horny Michael. Monday morning. COME ON! Teamocil. Or it could be your colon. I’d want to get in there and find some answers.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">O kay who d like a banger in.</title><link href="https://d2m.tech/webpacked-jekyll-assets-minima/jekyll/update/2016/10/18/o-kay-who-d-like-a-banger-in.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="O kay who d like a banger in." /><published>2016-10-18T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2016-10-18T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>https://d2m.tech/webpacked-jekyll-assets-minima/jekyll/update/2016/10/18/o-kay-who-d-like-a-banger-in</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://d2m.tech/webpacked-jekyll-assets-minima/jekyll/update/2016/10/18/o-kay-who-d-like-a-banger-in.html">&lt;p&gt;O-kay, who’d like a banger in the mouth? You want your belt to buckle, not your chair. I’m in Vegas this week and would like to point out the Blue Man Group is &lt;em&gt;actually&lt;/em&gt; hiring. The support group? Dead Dove DO NOT EAT. I’ve made a huge tiny mistake.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let me out that Queen. Family Love Michael.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hate the Wetlands. They’re stupid and wet, and there are bugs everywhere, and I think I maced a crane. Well, obviously, I’m not a big guy. I’m not a Carl Weathers, par example. Mr. Zuckerkorn, you’ve been warned about touching. You said spanking. I’d rather be dead in California than alive in Arizona. Now, do you wanna steer, or are you too old to sit on your Pop’s lap and drive? ¡Soy loco por los Cornballs! Oh, hi, Mom. I have the afternoon free. Really? Did “nothing” cancel?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stop it, stop it. This objectification of women has to stop. Michael: It’s just Mom and whores. I’m sure Egg is a great person. She’s a girl, I need to teach her how to be a woman. Within her lies a queen. Let me out that queen. What is she doing at a beauty pageant? Is she running the lights or something? Friday night. I was set up. By the Brits. A group of British builders operating outside the O.C.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hear the jury’s still out on science. With spicy club sauce. That’s so you can videotape it when they put you in a naked pyramid and point to your Charlie Browns. Buster, you remember when we were kissing last night? Buster: It was a wild, wild ride.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What’s next, Michael? Are you going to make dancing illegal? Is this the tiny town from Footloose? Wow. We’re just blowing through nap time, aren’t we. Dead Dove DO NOT EAT. If mother sees this, she will blow a cow. God knows they’re squinters. She keeps saying that God is going to show me a sign. The… something of my ways. Probably out there without a flipper, swimming around in a circle, freaking out his whole family. Pound is tic-tac-toe, right?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When a man needs to prove to a woman that he’s actually… When a man loves a woman… What’s gotten into you? Have you been eating cheese?  Hahahahah! ♪♪ It ain’t easy being white. It ain’t easy being brown. ♪♪ I’d rather be dead in California than alive in Arizona. When a man needs to prove to a woman that he’s actually… When a man loves a woman… I hear the jury’s still out on science. Let’s see some bananas and nuts! Heyyyyyy, Uncle Father Oscar.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yeah, that’s a cultural problem is what it is. You know, your average American male is in a perpetual state of adolescence, you know, arrested development. (Hey. That’s the name of the show!) I just don’t want him to point out my cracker ass in front of Ann. I am having a love affair with this ice cream sandwich. If you didn’t have adult onset diabetes, I wouldn’t mind giving you a little sugar. I was set up. By the Brits. A group of British builders operating outside the O.C. Look at us, crying like a bunch of girls on the last day of camp. Heyyyy uncle father Oscar.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Michael, I’m your older brother. I’ll never be proud of you. You need to do more with Rita. Believe me, I’d like to. I don’t want no part of yo tight-ass country club, ya freak bitch! Yes. Lindsay and I are planning a night of heterosexual intercourse. Each year, Oscar attempts the four hundred mile walk from Newport Beach to Berkeley, California. In the twelve years that he’s attempted this, he’s never made it farther than UC Irvine. And here you are coming out of your mother’s third base! Ohhh little guy. The tears aren’t coming. The tears just aren’t coming. It’s sort of like going from prime rib to… I don’t know… weird brother of prime rib.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Teamocil. I am going to my spin class. I thought you had vertigo. Today I learned this is a real place, tho more lush than the OC. I prematurely shot my wad on what was supposed to be a dry run, so now I’m afraid I have something of a mess on my hands.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">O-kay, who’d like a banger in the mouth? You want your belt to buckle, not your chair. I’m in Vegas this week and would like to point out the Blue Man Group is actually hiring. The support group? Dead Dove DO NOT EAT. I’ve made a huge tiny mistake.</summary></entry></feed>